Which is probably the most radical thing
that's ever happened in hip-hop, period,
ever. Everything else I could think of
has been words, but like Tupac literally
found two crooked cops trying to assault
an unarmed black dude, and he popped
them, both of them, with a nine, and
went to court, and if he if he didn't
fight the case, they would have never
found out that these two cops had stolen
guns from the evidence lockers at their
police stations, and were drunk on the
job, and were harassing somebody. Like
his words are incredible. His history of
organizing in the free world and in
prison systems is unmatched. My favorite
rapper named Tupac. Love Tupac cuz he
shot two cops.
I got a 9 mm called Thug Life.
I got a new chain that say [__]
ice. Diamonds do go